＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?
((サスケ : 水月 いずれ お前を
ここから出してやる))
Suigetsu... I will release you from
this place some day.
(水月)やっぱり キミか
キミが ここに来たってことは➡
I knew it was you...
The fact that you're here must mean
you killed Orochimaru.
大蛇丸を倒したんだね。
ああ。
Yeah.
But never mind that.
Let's get you out of here.
そんなことより
ここから出してやる。
(水月)やっと出られた。
Free at last. Thank you, Sasuke.
ありがとう サスケ。
水月 まずは お前だ。
Suigetsu, you're the first.
一緒に来い。
Come with me.
まずは ボクが？
じゃあ 他にもいるの？
Me, first? There are others then?
あと２人 北アジトの重吾と
南アジトの香燐を連れていく。
Two others. I'm taking Jugo
from the northern hideout
and Karin from the southern hideout.
本当に？
Are you sure about that?
なんだ？
What is it?
いやね 好きじゃないから。
アイツら。
It's nothing...
Just that I don't like them.
仲よくは できないなと
そうね 思ってね フフッ。
I can't get along with them...
At least, that's what I think.
ボクを選ぶのは ともかく
あの２人を選ぶキミも➡
Sure, you picked me,
but I wonder about choosing
those two, Sasuke.
どうかと思うよ サスケ。
グダグダうるさい 服を着ろ。
行くぞ。
Enough with the rambling.
Put on your clothes.
We're going.
アハハ！ えらく上からの
もの言いじゃないか。
Ordering me around like a big shot, eh?
キミと ボクの関係を
はっきりさせておこうか ねえ？
Let me clarify the relationship
between you and me...
All right?
悪いけど ボクを助けたのは
キミの都合だ。
Sorry, but you chose  to rescue me.
ボクは キミについて行くなんて
一言も言ってない。
I never said anything about following you.
大蛇丸を倒したからって
キミが上ってわけじゃない。
Just because you defeated Orochimaru
doesn't make you better than me.
みんな 狙っていた。
Everyone was after him.
キミは お気に入りで
監禁されることもなく➡
You were Orochimaru's pet,
so you weren't imprisoned
and you stayed by his side.
大蛇丸の側にいた。
やれるチャンスが みんなよりも
多かっただけだからね。
You had more chances to kill him
than the rest of us.
Gotcha... Just kidding.
なんてね 冗談だよ。
だけど今 キミを見逃したことで➡
But I let you go just now,
so that makes us even.
ボクを助けた貸しは
チャラにしてもらうよ。
やっと自由になれたんだ
ボクは ボクの好きにさせてもらう。
I'm free at last,
so I'm going to do as I please.
そうか 残念だ。
I see.
That's unfortunate.
そういえば キミの小隊だったね。
By the way...
It was your team, wasn't it?
ボクの大先輩
百地再不斬を倒したのは。
The team that brought down
my great predecessor, Zabuza Momochi.
再不斬の刀 首切り包丁って
どうなったのかな？
Whatever happened to his blade...
the Executioner's Blade?
ねぇ こうしようよ。
Let's do this.
If you tell me where the blade is,
and I take possession of it,
キミがそのありかを教えてくれて➡
ボクがその刀を
手に入れることができたら➡
キミを手伝ってもいいよ。
then I'll be willing to help you.
服を着ろ。
Put some clothes on.
Zabuza's Blade
GREAT NARUTO BRIDGE
フン。
なると大橋？
The Great Naruto Bridge?
変な名前だね。
What a weird name...
ねぇ 再不斬先輩は強かったかい？
Say, was the great Zabuza Senpai strong?
((カカシ : 全員ふせろ！
Everyone, duck!
(カカシ)終わりだ。
It's over.
(再不斬)そう甘かねえんだよ！
I'm not that naïve!
(サクラ)カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei!
《しまった！》
Damn it!
くっ…。
お前らみたいなのは
忍者とは呼ばねえ。
Guys like you aren't called "Ninja"...
(ただのガキだ))
Just mere kids.
どうしたの サスケ。 サスケ！
What's the matter, Sasuke?
Sasuke?
何でもない 行くぞ。
Nothing. Let's go.
はっ…。
ないよ。 ねぇサスケ
ホントにここにあったの？
It's not here.
Say, Sasuke, are you sure it was here?
ああ。
でもないね。 どうしてかな？
Yeah.
But it's not here. I wonder why?
さあな。
オレはその墓の番人じゃない。
How would I know?
I'm not the keeper of that grave.
ないなら
誰かが持って行ったんだろう。
If it's not there,
someone must've taken it.
それはそうだろうね。
ひとりで歩いていくわけないし。
You're right about that.
It wouldn't have walked off on its own.
サスケ 悪いけどあの刀がない以上➡
Sasuke...
Sorry, but without the blade here,
me joining you will have to wait.
キミについて行くのは後回しだね。
どうするつもりだ？
What'll you do then?
もちろん 探し出すよ。
What else? I'm gonna look for it.
忍刀七人衆の刀は➡
The blade of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist was passed down
代々受け継がれていくシステムだった。
from generation to generation.
That was the system.
ボクも七人衆に憧れて
修業を積んできたからね。
I aspired to become one of them
and trained for it.
再不斬先輩がいない以上➡
Since Zabuza Senpai is gone...
あの首切り包丁は
ボクが持つべき刀なんだ。
I'm the one who should possess
that Executioner's Blade.
(ゾウリ)どこ見て
歩いてんだ この野郎 バカ野郎！
Watch where you're walking, you idiot!
あん？ おうおう 何か
文句でもあんのか にいちゃ…。
Huh?
What? You have a problem, Bro?
。…ちゃ～に かのんあ
もでくんもかんな うおうお
Ah...whatever...
チッ！ 気をつけろよ！
Just be careful!
んだ！ バカ野郎 アホ野郎
アホロートル野郎 ボケ！
What's his problem, stupid...
jerk... old fart... idiot...?!
優しいなぁ サスケは！
You're so nice, Sasuke...
で このおとしまえは
どうつけてくれるのかな？
So...how're you gonna settle this debt?
あぁ！
Oh...
う～ん フフフ！ ヨーグルト最高！
This yogurt is the best.
こういうの久しぶりなんだぁ！
It's been so long since
I had anything like this.
ずっと水槽のなかにいたからね！
I was in a water tank all this time.
のんびりしていていいのか？
Can you afford to relax like this?
っていうか。
But...you're the one in a rush.
急いでるのは
キミのほうなんだろ？
いったい ボクらを集めて
どうするつもり？
Why're you gathering us
together anyway?
３人が揃ったときに話す。
I'll tell you when we've all assembled.
ふ～ん。 よ～し！
天下でもとっちゃおう！
"All right, let's go conquer this world!"
なんて言い出したりして！
You're not gonna say something
like that, are you?
そんなものは
お前たちで好きにしろ。
Do that on your own time.
オレがとるものは…。
I'm aiming for...
something much bigger.
もっとでかい。
他のヤツがそんな話をしても
まったく信じられないけど➡
If anyone else started saying that,
I wouldn't believe it for a second.
キミが言うとね～。
But with you...
ホントなのかなって思えるのが
不思議だよね。
I think maybe it's possible...
And that's the strange thing.
あっ ねぇ キミ。
なると大橋だったっけ？
Oh say...
The Great Naruto Bridge, was it?
あの橋の近くに➡
Ever heard of a large blade
near that bridge?
大きな刀があったの
知らないかい？
はぁ ええ。
そういえばあったような。
Well... Oh, maybe there was...
それが？
What about it?
彼が その刀を探しているんだ。
He's looking for that blade.
えぇっ!?
あ あの 誰か知ってるかも！
Huh?! S-Someone might know about it...
I'll go and ask!
聞いてきます！ や～ん！
Oh dear!
SCREAMS
キミってモテるんだね！
You're quite the ladies' man, eh?
I know!
川辺に住んでる！
タズナさんなら！
- Tazuna...
- Who lives by the riverside...
知ってるんじゃないでしょうか！
...would know!
タズナか…。
Tazuna...huh?
誰 タズナって？
Who is this Tazuna?
あの橋をつくった
大工の頭領だ。
The carpenter boss who built that bridge.
頭なら今はいないぜ。
The boss isn't here right now.
どこに行ったのかな？
Do you know where he went?
雷の国だよ。 橋の工事に
イナリを連れて出かけてらぁ。
To the Land of Lightning to build a bridge.
He took Inari with him.
あと１年は帰ってこねえよ！
He won't be back for another year.
カミナリの国かぁ 遠いな。
The Land of Lightning, eh?
That's very far.
なると大橋の近くに➡
Do you know of a large blade that
was left near the Great Naruto Bridge?
大きな刀があったのを
知らないか？
ああ あれね。
Oh, that.
大黒天善が持っていったんだよ。
Tenzen Daikoku took it.
本当は あの刀を使っていた忍者を
捕まえに来たんだけど➡
He originally came here to capture
the Ninja who wielded the blade.
死んでるってんで
代わりにあの刀を➡
But after learning the Ninja was dead,
he took the blade with him instead.
持っていったんだってよ。
まいったなぁ。
大黒天善か…。
Damn it... Tenzen Daikoku, eh?
水の国の大名の
側近だったヤツだよ。
He was the aide to
the lord of the Land of Water.
再不斬先輩が霧隠れで
クーデターを起こしたとき➡
Apparently, many of his men were killed
during Zabuza Senpai's coup d'état
in the Hidden Mist.
ずいぶんと
手下がやられたらしいよ。
そのことを
根にもっていたんだなぁ。
I guess he had a grudge from back then.
テメエ どこに目をつけて…！
Where the hell...
do you think you're--?!
やあ！ キミのこと➡
Hey, we were just looking for you.
ちょうど捜してたんだ！
うわっ!!
うわ～っ!!
な… 何なんだよ オメエら!?
Wh-Who are you guys?!
だって キミ
裏事情とか詳しそうだし。
You seem like the type to know
all kinds of things...
オレは 天善のことなんて
知らねえよ！
I know nothing about Tenzen!
知ってることだけでいいんだけど
話してくれないかな？
Anything will do.
Just tell us what you know.
あ… あっ…。
(ゾウリ)だ… 大黒天善は
政治家だが それは表の顔で➡
T-Tenzen Daikoku is a politician...
But there's another side to him.
裏じゃ 大盗賊団を率いる頭領だ。
He's the boss of a huge band of thieves.
巨額のワイロを 大名に渡して➡
I hear he doles out huge bribes
to the feudal lords,
好き放題に
悪事を働いてるって話だ。
and gets to do whatever
evil things he likes.
ちゃんと知ってるじゃん。
で どこに住んでるの？
See, you know it all. And?
Where does he live?
(ゾウリ)南の外れ
森の中に建つ城だ。
Just to the south...
there's a castle in the forest.
その城は 数千の傭兵に守られて
難攻不落だってウワサだ。
Rumor says several thousand mercenaries
guard the place and that it's impenetrable.
(天善)うん!?
だ… 誰だ!? どこから入った？
Wh-Who's there? How did you get in?!
明後日 数万の兵を引き連れ
この城を落としにくる。
The day after tomorrow,
this castle will be attacked by
tens of thousands of soldiers.
ありったけの兵隊を集めておけ。
Make sure you gather
every man available.
オレの名は… 水月。
My name...is Suigetsu.
(天善)曲者だ!!
出あえ！ 出あえ！
An intruder! Men! Come out!
(水月)まったく…。
Cripes... What's going on?
どうなってんだよ？
明日 他の豪族が
数万の軍勢を引き連れて➡
It seems another powerful clan plans
to attack Tenzen's castle tomorrow
with an army that numbers
in the tens of thousands.
天善の城に攻め込むらしい。
へえ～ それ ホントなの？
Oh... is that true?
あ～あ… まあ いっか。
Oh well, whatever.
敵が混乱すれば
チャンスは増えるし➡
The more confused the enemy becomes,
the better my chances.
千人が万人になろうと
忍者であるボクには関係ないしね。
Be it several thousand
or tens of thousands,
it doesn't matter to a Ninja like me.
首切り包丁は 今夜にでも
忍び込んでとってくるよ。
I'll sneak in tonight and
take the Executioner's Blade.
ひとつ 賭けをしないか？
How about making a wager?
賭け？
A wager...?
どちらが先に
首切り包丁を手に入れるか。
On who gets
the Executioner's Blade first...
アハハ！ キミに そんな遊び心が
あるなんて思わなかったよ。
Huh?! I never expected you
to have a playful side!
やろうよ。 おもしろそうだ。
Let's do it. It sounds like fun.
では 今からだ。
Then it starts now.
There's only one rule.
We don't kill anyone.
ルールは ひとつ。
誰ひとり殺さぬこと。
えっ？
Huh?
なんだ キサマは！
Who the hell are you?!
怪しいヤツめ！
You're suspicious!
キミ… 今からって…。
You mean... Now as in...?
ホント 今からなんだね。
It really starts now, huh?
フゥ… 賭けに
負けるわけにはいかないし…。
I can't lose this wager.
Well, all right, let's do it.
いいよ つきあうよ。
フゥ…。
火遁 豪火球の術！
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
ひょ～ さすがサスケ！
Gotta hand it to you, Sasuke!
…って お前！ いないのかよ!?
What the--?! He's gone?!
(みんな)うお～！
マジですか？
Is this for real?!
(みんな)うお～！
くっ！ いっちょいくか！
Damn, may as well get started!
でやっ！
フゥ… さすがに疲れるね。
やっとゴールだ。
This is tiring, after all.
Finally, my goal.
バカな… あれだけの軍勢を
たった一人で倒したのか!?
Impossible... You defeated
all those men by yourself?!
まあね。
Well yeah. Even with legitimate weapons,
attacking me is useless.
ボクには まともな武器できても
無意味だから。
くっ…！
If legitimate weapons are of no use...!
まともな武器でダメなら
こいつは どうだ～!!
How about...this?!
Say, that's my Executioner's Blade.
あっ！ そいつは
ボクの首切り包丁じゃないか！
おお！ やったか!?
Ah, you did it!
最後の最後で油断しおったな。
フハハハハハッ！
You let down your guard at the very end.
(水月)ハハハハ！
おっ!?
ごめんね。
ボクには刃物は通用しないんだよ。
Sorry. Blades don't work on me...
ねっ。
You see?
でも うらやましいよ。
But I'm jealous.
特別な訓練がなくても
その刀を振り回せるなんて。
You're able to wield that blade
without any special training...
体格がいいと得だよね。
It helps when you have a good physique.
うっ… ぬお～！
うっ！
町で言いふらしているんだって？
I hear you've been telling
everyone in town...
鬼人 再不斬を殺して
その刀を奪ったんだ って。
That you killed the Demon Zabuza
and took that blade from him.
Th-That wasn't me...
It was Lord Tenzen who...
そ… それは
オレではなく天善様が…。
Hmm... So you killed Zabuza Senpai?
へぇ～ アンタが再不斬先輩をね。
N-No... The one who killed Zabuza was...
ち… 違う！
再不斬をやったのは…！
Zabuza?
再不斬？
Err...no! The one who killed Mr. Zabuza
wasn't me...
(天善)あぁ～ いや！
再不斬さんを殺したのは➡
オレじゃなくて その… うっ！
お前は 昨日の…。
You're...the one...from yesterday!
あっ！ アイツだ！
He's the one!
He's the one who killed Mr. Zabuza!
アイツが 再不斬さんを殺したんだ！
オレは その刀を
墓から持ってきただけだ！
All I did was bring the blade
back from the grave!
グッ！ フハハハハ！
くしくも０点じゃないよ！
I'll give you some points for that.
悪党が とっさについたウソにしちゃ
気が利いてる。
That's a pretty good lie for a villain
like you to come up with.
ハハハハハハ！
水月。
Suigetsu!
How thoughtful.
I was feeling a bit dehydrated.
気が利くね ちょっと
脱水症状気味だったんだよね。
勘違いしてるようだけど➡
I think you're under
the wrong impression here.
ボクと再不斬さんとは
べつに親しくも何ともないんだよ。
I wasn't particularly close to Mr. Zabuza.
ただね同郷の先輩がね。
But the thought of my Senpai
from my village...
うお～!!
うわぁ～!!
こんな弱っちい連中に
やられたなんて➡
...having such pathetic rumors about
losing to weaklings like you is...
無様なウワサを
たてられるのも… なんてね。
You know...?
キサマら こんなことをして
ただで済むと思ってるのか。
D-Do you think you can
get away with this?!
おとしまえは つけないとねえ。
Well, you'll have to pay for this...right?
アンタで試し切りをさせてもらうよ。
ひっ!?
I think I'll test it on you.
やめておけ
そんなヤツを斬って何になる。
Forget it. What's the sense
in killing someone like him?
フッ。
ああ!!
I've cut through the main pillars,
so you'd better get out of here.
大黒柱を斬ったから
早くここから出たほうがいいよ。
命だけは助けてあげる。
I'll spare your life.
サスケに免じてね。
Out of respect for you, Sasuke.
サスケ？ まさか
あの大蛇丸を殺った サスケなのか？
へえ キミって有名人なんだね。
こんなとこまで
名前が響いているなんてさ。
うぅ… うお！
ああ～!!
ハハハハハハハ！
フフ この刀があれば
キミにも負けない… かもね。
あのさ キミ ボクが刀欲しいって
言い出すとわかってたんでしょ。
それに 最初から あの墓に
刀がないことも知っていた。
そうか。
わざわざ あの城に兵隊集めさせる
情報を流したのも➡
キミ？
天善 キミと会ったような
口ぶりだったし。
なに 賭けとか言ったのも➡
わざわざ ボクを敵のただ中に
追い込むため？
もしかして試したの？
このボクを。
ハハッ ひどいことするな。
ケガでもしたら
どうするつもりだよ。
でも これでよくわかったよ
キミって人がさ。
まあ それでこそ
ボクのイメージどおりのサスケだよ。
刀は手に入れたから
約束どおり力は貸すけどさ。
…で どっちから行くの？
あっ 待って
近いほうからだよね。
キミのことは
少しわかってきたんだ。
それがキミらしい答えだし。
フッ そう 近いほうからだ。
ぐわ～!!
(香燐)大蛇丸が死んだからって
勝手されちゃ困るんだよ！
《このチャクラの感じ ま まさか…》
＜港町 ハルジオン。
今 ここを出港した
フェアリーテイルの船があった。
８組の魔導士たちを乗せ➡
いざ 天狼島へ＞